http://www.fantasticfiction.co.uk/privacy.htm

Privacy Statement for Fantastic Fiction
Fantastic Fiction has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We believe we have a fundamental duty to keep your data private and secure so you can have confidence when using our website. Please read the policy carefully.
This policy applies to the website Fantastic Fiction
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, our practices, or your dealings with this site please contact webmaster@fantasticfiction.com
This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Fantastic Fiction when you sign up to Fantasticfiction.com, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
By registering your email address you are accepting this privacy policy and authorise Fantastic Fiction to collect, store and process your information in the ways explained.
What information do we collect?
Personal Information
Fantastic Fiction Visitors: we do not collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Fantastic Fiction Members: when you sign up become a member, we ask you to provide us with your name and email address which we subsequently use to notify you of new books.
You can change or delete this information at any time when signed in.
Email correspondents: if you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.
Fantastic Fiction does not share any personal information with any third party.
Cookies Information
Like most websites Fantastic Fiction uses both session and persistent cookies to ensure you get the best experience from our site. Please see our Cookie Policy
Log File Information
We do not collect any server log file information.
Clear Gifs information
When you use Fantastic Fiction, we employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our members to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, to improve the effectiveness of our service, and make Fantastic Fiction better for our users.
How we use your information
Personal information
For Fantastic Fiction members we use the name and email address you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service
Fantastic Fiction never discloses your personal information to any third party.
Non-personal information
We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Fantastic Fiction. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name or email address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
If you would like more information about this practice and to know about not having this information used by these companies please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Special Relationships
Fantastic Fiction is an associate of a number of on-line retailers. Please see our affiliate disclosure.
External Links
This site contains links to other websites.
Fantastic Fiction is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those websites.
Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our Web site, is subject to that website's own rules and policies.
How We Protect Your Information
To protect the privacy and security of Fantastic Fiction members, we require a unique password to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from Fantastic Fiction.
Children's Privacy
The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) applies to citizens of the European Union and contains specific rules designed to boost the protection of children’s personal data. It restricts the age at which data subjects can lawfully give consent, and regulates the way online services obtain children’s consent.
Under the GDPR, the default age at which a person is no longer considered a child is 16, but it allows member states to adjust that limit to anywhere between 13 and 16.
Fantastic Fiction does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under their country's age of consent, or knowingly allow such persons to register.
Fantastic Fiction membership is not intended for children under 16. If you are under 16, please do not sign up to become a member of Fantastic Fiction or send any information about yourself to us, including your name or email address. No one under age 16 should
provide any personal information to Fantastic Fiction.
If a parent or guardian learns that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16 without their consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about your child, please contact webmaster@fantasticfiction.com
This privacy policy was last modified on September 20, 2020.
Search for  AuthorBookSeries
© 1999 -
Fantastic Fiction
Questions? Comments? Corrections? Please email webmaster@fantasticfiction.com
About Fantastic Fiction       Privacy Policy       Cookie Policy       Terms       Affiliate disclosure       Preferences
Top
